JUSTINE YOUNG

I am a UX designer interested in joining a collaborative design team that is working on creating innovative solutions in software and technology.

Having worked with a startup on an AR mobile app, I would love to design comprehensive user experiences with a wider reach and bigger impact.

www.justinehyoung.com

justinehyoung@gmail.com Irvine, CA 92606 510-693-5251

SKILLS

Information Architecture
Interaction Design
Personas & User Flows
UI/UX Design
User Research
User Testing
Rapid Prototyping
Responsive Design
Wireframing
Logo/Branding Strategy
Visual Design

TOOLS

Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe InDesign
Adobe XD
Sketch
Figma
InVision
HTML
CSS
Javascript
GitHub
Wordpress
Hotjar
Jira

EXPERIENCE

The Portal

UI/UX Designer | August, 2018 - Present

- Work closely with client as sole UI/UX Designer
- Translate wireframes utilizing UX best practices and user feedback in collaboration with the business requirements of client company
- Redesign digital marketing landing page and maintain Wordpress website by implementing UI designs that follow company's style guide

Business Operations Manager | February, 2018 - Present

- Supervise interns by handling correspondence between web development, digital marketing, and sales teams
- Consult digital marketing leads by designing project proposals to present during sales meetings
- Lead group of ~10 interns to host investor/startup events of 200+ attendees
- Create and update documentation of our hosted events and operations after iterating and improving each process

PROJECTS

HoardBoard | Cloud storage prototype [View Case Study]
A concept design for fans to collaborate, upload, and organize images.
User Research, Wireframing, Testing, Branding, and Visual Design using paper, Figma, and UsabilityHub.

AR Medical Application | Mobile UI (NDA blocked)

Worked with stakeholder by translating user flows to low-fidelity wireframes. Delivered high-fidelity prototype and assets to client and developers. UI for Wireframe, Visual Design, and Prototype in Sketch.

The Portal - Digital Marketing | Landing Page [View Here] Designed and implemented a lead generation page with the digital marketing team using Wordpress. I also redesigned the page utilizing UX design best practices to improve the flow and visual design for the page.

EDUCATION

University of California | Irvine, 2017 BS, Biological Sciences

Bloc, 2018 - PresentDesign and Frontend Apprenticeship